export const fullStack = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'What does the term "full-stack development" refer to?',
        options: [
          'Developing only the front end of a web application',
          'Developing both the front end and back end of a web application',
          'Developing mobile applications',
          'Designing user interfaces only',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Developing both the front end and back end of a web application',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which programming language is commonly used for both front-end and back-end development?',
        options: ['JavaScript', 'Python', 'Java', 'Ruby'],
        correctAnswer: 'JavaScript',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is the purpose of the "React" library in full-stack development?',
        options: [
          'To handle server-side logic',
          'To manage databases',
          'To build user interfaces on the client side',
          'To perform data analysis',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'To build user interfaces on the client side',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is the role of a RESTful API in a full-stack application?',
        options: [
          'To handle client-side routing',
          'To connect the front end with the back end through HTTP requests',
          'To manage database queries',
          'To provide a user interface',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'To connect the front end with the back end through HTTP requests',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'In the context of full-stack development, what is a "MERN" stack?',
        options: [
          'A stack of papers on a desk',
          'MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js',
          'Machine Learning, Ethereum, React, Node.js',
          'Microsoft, Express.js, React, Nest.js',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is the purpose of a server in the context of full-stack development?',
        options: [
          'To store and manage data',
          'To run JavaScript code in the browser',
          'To handle client-side routing',
          'To provide resources and process requests from clients',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'To provide resources and process requests from clients',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Which database is commonly used in full-stack development for storing relational data?',
        options: ['MongoDB', 'MySQL', 'Firebase', 'Redis'],
        correctAnswer: 'MySQL',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is the purpose of the "npm start" command in a full-stack project?',
        options: [
          'To install new packages',
          'To start the development server',
          'To build the production version of the project',
          'To deploy the application',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'To start the development server',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is the role of version control systems (e.g., Git) in full-stack development?',
        options: [
          'To manage the appearance of the user interface',
          'To control the version of the programming language used',
          'To track changes in the codebase and collaborate with others',
          'To optimize database queries',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'To track changes in the codebase and collaborate with others',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is the purpose of the "dotenv" package in a full-stack Node.js project?',
        options: [
          'To create environment variables',
          'To generate random data',
          'To parse JSON files',
          'To validate form inputs',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'To create environment variables',
        userAnswer: null,
      },
]